geekspie.com 2018-08-26

# Cookies and Privacy Policy - Geeks Pie

At Geekspie.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us and we take it very seriously.

## Personal Information

As with most other websites, we collect the data you provide to us when you visit or post a comment to our site. This information may include your name, your email address, your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer, Chrome, Safari or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. Your personal information will never be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside Geekspie.com.

### Cookies

Cookies consist of portions of code installed in the browser that assist the Owner in providing the Service according to the purposes described. Some of the purposes for which Cookies are installed may also require the User’s consent.

Where the installation of Cookies is based on consent, such consent can be freely withdrawn at any time following the instructions provided in this document.

## Analytics

The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.

### Google Analytics with anonymized IP (Google Inc.)

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of Geekspie.com, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.

This integration of Google Analytics anonymizes your IP address. It works by shortening Users’ IP addresses within member states of the European Union or in other contracting states to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will the complete IP address be sent to a Google server and shortened within the US.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

## Advertising

This type of service allows User Data to be utilized for advertising communication purposes displayed in the form of banners and other advertisements on Geekspie.com.

In addition to any opt out offered by any of the services below, the User may opt out of a third-party service’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1).

### Google AdSense (Google Inc.) [non-personalized ads served to EU Users]

Google AdSense is an advertising service provided by Google Inc. This service uses the “Doubleclick” Cookie, which tracks use of Geekspie.com and User behavior concerning ads, products and services offered.

Users may decide to disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on: [google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout](https://adssettings.google.com/anonymous?sig=ACi0TCjXh3YYktqMJkhq3qg9NYL20HDVvtUoguu6qaEgtmeO2YUJIzEKsjy_yI0gxlXpXQmHHMETk_gvtuORSSz5dXsPrQotGdnH5oPmzLgt2A-CVN2zmjI&hl=en)

Personal Data collected: Cookies and Usage Data

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads) – [Opt Out](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout)

## Traffic Optimization and Distribution

This type of service allows Geekspie.com to distribute their content using servers located across different countries and to optimize their performance.

Which Personal Data are processed depends on the characteristics and the way these services are implemented. Their function is to filter communications between Geekspie.com and the User’s browser.

### CloudFlare

CloudFlare is a traffic optimization and distribution service provided by CloudFlare Inc.

The way CloudFlare is integrated means that it filters all the traffic through Geekspie.com, i.e., communication between Geekspie.com and the User’s browser, while also allowing analytical data from Geekspie.com to be collected.

Personal Data collected: Cookies and various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service.

Place of processing: United States – [Privacy Policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy/)

## How to provide or withdraw consent to the installation of Cookies

In addition to what is specified in this document, the User can manage preferences for Cookies directly from within their own browser and prevent – for example – third parties from installing Cookies.

Through browser preferences, it is also possible to delete Cookies installed in the past, including the Cookies that may have saved the initial consent for the installation of Cookies by this website.

Users can, for example, can find information about how to manage Cookies in the most commonly used browsers at the following addresses:

With regard to Cookies installed by third parties, Users can manage their preferences and withdrawal of their consent by clicking the related opt-out link (if provided), by using the means provided in the third party’s privacy policy, or by contacting the third party.

Notwithstanding the above, the Owner informs that Users may follow the instructions provided on the subsequently linked initiatives by the [EDAA](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) (EU), the [Network Advertising Initiative](https://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-digital-advertising) (US) and the [Digital Advertising Alliance](https://www.aboutads.info/consumers/) (US), [DAAC](https://youradchoices.ca/understanding-online-advertising/) (Canada), [DDAI](http://www.ddai.info/optout) (Japan) or other similar services. Such initiatives allow Users to select their tracking preferences for most of the advertising tools. The Owner thus recommends that Users make use of these resources in addition to the information provided in this document.

## Contact Details

Email: admin@Geekspie.com

Since the installation of third-party Cookies and other tracking systems through the services used within Geekspie.com cannot be technically controlled by the Owner, any specific references to Cookies and tracking systems installed by third parties are to be considered indicative. In order to obtain complete information, the User is kindly requested to consult the privacy policy for the respective third-party services listed in this document.

Given the objective complexity surrounding the identification of technologies based on Cookies, Users are encouraged to contact the Owner should they wish to receive any further information on the use of Cookies by Geekspie.com.

This website or its third party tools use cookies, which are necessary to its functioning and required to achieve the purposes illustrated in the cookie policy. If you want to know more or withdraw your consent to all or some of the cookies, please refer to the [cookie policy](http://geekspie.com/cookies-privacy-policy/). By closing this banner, scrolling this page or continuing to browse otherwise, you agree to the the use of cookies.Close
